{
    "subject": "resource/Sister_Act",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Harvey_Keitel",
    "human_readable": "Sister Act stars Harvey Keitel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.660896897315979,
            "question": "What movie stars Harvey Keitel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6334575414657593,
            "question": "Who is in the cast of Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5227020978927612,
            "question": "What are some other popular movies starring Harvey Keitel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4486240744590759,
            "question": "What other genres has Harvey Keitel acted in besides comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4152679145336151,
            "question": "Are there any sequels to Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40237918496131897,
            "question": "Is Harvey Keitel known for any musical roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3351433277130127,
            "question": "What is Harvey Keitel's most famous role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29122745990753174,
            "question": "Did Sister Act win any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2535248100757599,
            "question": "What is the overall plot of Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22157317399978638,
            "question": "How was the reception of Sister Act by critics and audiences?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sister Act stars Harvey Keitel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3306_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall plot of Sister Act?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3306_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Sister Act win any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3306_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Harvey Keitel's most famous role?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3306_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3306_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query \"Sister Act stars Harvey Keitel\":\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents provided contain information that confirms Harvey Keitel's involvement in the movie Sister Act, including being listed as a star or playing a specific role (Eddie Souther) in the film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Sister Act features Harvey Keitel as one of its starring actors. Therefore, the triple \"Sister Act stars Harvey Keitel\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}